[laughs]
Does the smell of your underarms also make
people around you feel the same way?  So
this product Pitku has come on Shark Tank Season Five.
This has been started by the girl, that is, the
actress.  If you know his name, please
tell me in the comments.  They say that if you
apply it continuously for a month, you will
never have any smell.  This is for
₹999.
So I have applied it after taking bath.  This is
a
very pure form of what we used to have as Fatkadi.  But this is an extra
step after bathing.  It has
no smell, no gas, nothing.  Meaning but let's see whether
this product is useful or not.
Get up brother, it seems I will have to wait a month.  Also don't forget to
subscribe to.   Guys,
I am not born with Fitku.
[Laughter]